{
    "subject": "resource/Bill_Gates",
    "predicate": "ontology/spouse",
    "object": "resource/Melinda_Gates",
    "human_readable": "Bill Gates' spouse is Melinda Gates.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833692908287048,
            "question": "Is Melinda Gates Bill Gates' wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9753419756889343,
            "question": "Is Melinda Gates married to Bill Gates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8824859857559204,
            "question": "Who is Melinda Gates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8769453763961792,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Bill Gates and Melinda Gates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8434016704559326,
            "question": "Who is Bill Gates' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.800888180732727,
            "question": "Does Bill Gates have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723483681678772,
            "question": "To whom is Bill Gates married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6784655451774597,
            "question": "What is the name of Bill Gates' wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6738453507423401,
            "question": "Who is Melinda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5550716519355774,
            "question": "What is the name of Bill Gates' partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bill Gates' spouse is Melinda Gates.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8072_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Melinda?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8072_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Bill Gates' wife?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8072_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Bill Gates married?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8072_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8072_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention Melinda Gates as being married to Bill Gates and their divorce in 2021.\n* There are no contradictions or counter-evidence in the documents that suggest Melinda is not Bill's spouse.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage and divorce of Bill Gates and Melinda Gates, confirming that Melinda Gates was indeed Bill Gates' spouse."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}